<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Parsed by jbart3h -->
<resources>
     <string name="agree_and_next">Agree</string>
     <string name="album_introduction">Gallery allows you to manage, optimize, and edit photos and videos on your device, as well as sync them to Xiaomi Cloud.</string>
     <string name="application_package_introduction">This app allows you to install third party apps, scan them before installation, and give recommendations after it.</string>
     <string name="calculator_introduction">You can use this app for calculations, converting units and currencies, and estimating your mortgage repayments.</string>
     <string name="camera_introduction">You can use Camera to take photos and shoot videos.</string>
     <string name="carrier_introduction">"In order to provide you with better services, your device may periodically send your device version information, device identification data (including IMEI/IMSI/MSISDN/MAC address, MEID/ICCID), and approximate location information (including base station ID) to the carrier via Wi-Fi, mobile data network, or free SMS. The carrier promises to analyze relevant information only to improve the quality of services or to provide customized services or technologies, and won't disclose relevant information to third parties in any form that identifies you personally. The specific carrier statement shall prevail. Consult your carrier regarding the cost of using this service."</string>
     <string name="clock_introduction">You can use this app to view time, as well as use timer, world clock, stopwatch, set alarms, and more.</string>
     <string name="close_location_service_setting">You can choose turn off location access in Settings &gt; Additional settings &gt; Privacy or restrict permissions for individual apps in Security.</string>
     <string name="compass_introduction">You can use this app for navigation, as well as viewing coordinates, atmospheric pressure, and altitude.</string>
     <string name="content_introduction">Content Center aggregates content and services from multiple channels. Here you can read articles, watch videos, view daily featured items, and receive content recommendations.</string>
     <string name="diagnose_report">Send diagnostic data to locate and analyze system issues and improve user experience. Such data may include personal information (e.g. IP, location, etc.)</string>
     <string name="disageement_abnormal_download">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this service."</string>
     <string name="disagreement_abnormal_running">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose not to use this app or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases."</string>
     <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_application">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose not to use this app in such cases."</string>
     <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_product">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this product. You can choose not to use this product in such cases."</string>
     <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_service">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this service. You can choose not to use this service in such cases."</string>
     <string name="disagreement_exit_app">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose to sign out or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases."</string>
     <string name="disagreement_function">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this feature. You can choose not to use this feature in such cases."</string>
     <string name="disagreement_location_service">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this service."</string>
     <string name="disagreement_terminate_service">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose to uninstall, sign out, or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases."</string>
     <string name="download_introduction">This app manages all your downloads, including those done in GetApps, Mi Video, Updater, Themes, and Browser.</string>
     <string name="fast_application_introduction">Quick apps Framework allows you to create and provide services in quick apps.</string>
     <string name="font_hint_large">Default text size</string>
     <string name="font_hint_normal">Increase text size</string>
     <string name="framework_introduction">Mi Services Framework allows you to use Mi Account, Mi Push, Mi Stats, and MIUI BI.</string>
     <string name="framwork_base_service">To provide you with these services, Mi Services Framework (MiAccount, Mi Push, Mi Stats, MIUI BI) needs to connect to the internet, access your phone number, IMEI, and IMSI, and allow your device to receive push notifications</string>
     <string name="game_introduction">Games plug-in allows you to sign in, create orders, complete payments, use coupons, and participate in promotion events.</string>
     <string name="google_service_introduction">To be able to work normally, Google Play needs to connect to the internet, access your location, be able to record audio, make calls, access calendar events, call history, sensors, storage, camera, device info, and accounts.</string>
     <string name="location_introduction">Location-based services find products and services near you.</string>
     <string name="lockscreen_introduction">Wallpaper Carousel allows you to get fresh images delivered to your Lock screen daily.</string>
     <string name="note_introduction">This app allows you to create, view, and edit notes.</string>
     <string name="other_settings_ad_dialog_content">"After turning this feature off, you'll no longer receive personalized ads. However, you'll still receive ads that are irrelevant to your interests. You can learn more about personalized ads in Xiaomi Privacy Policy.
Turn off personalized ads anyway?"</string>
     <string name="other_settings_ad_disable_summary">Turn on to personalize ads</string>
     <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen_privacy_index">Privacy Policy</string>
     <string name="permission_account">Access accounts on your device:</string>
     <string name="permission_account_introduction">For signing in with Mi Account</string>
     <string name="permission_application_package_introduction">For accessing storage in order to parse and scan installation packages</string>
     <string name="permission_call_records">Access call history:</string>
     <string name="permission_call_records_introduction">For accessing call history in order to display blocked items</string>
     <string name="permission_call_state_introduction">For accessing phone status, recording calls, and pausing recordings during incoming calls</string>
     <string name="permission_clock_info_introduction">For saving alarm data</string>
     <string name="permission_contact">Access contacts:</string>
     <string name="permission_contact_introduction">For providing Blocklist functionality and calling emergency contacts</string>
     <string name="permission_different_device_introduction">For identifying services associated with different devices</string>
     <string name="permission_different_info_introduction">For identifying different devices</string>
     <string name="permission_direct_call">Make calls:</string>
     <string name="permission_direct_call_introduction">For adding items to Blocklist</string>
     <string name="permission_download_introduction">For caching downloaded items and saving them on your device</string>
     <string name="permission_imei_service">For accessing IMEI to provide services associated with your device</string>
     <string name="permission_interaction_introduction">For saving photos and videos on device</string>
     <string name="permission_location">Access location info:</string>
     <string name="permission_location_introduction">For providing location-based services</string>
     <string name="permission_log_introduction">For saving logs</string>
     <string name="permission_login_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts</string>
     <string name="permission_message_introduction">For sending messages to blocked contacts</string>
     <string name="permission_phone_imei_device">For accessing IMEI in order to identify devices</string>
     <string name="permission_phone_network">For accessing network type in order to optimize and adjust downloadable items</string>
     <string name="permission_phone_service">Access phone number, IMEI, and IMSI:</string>
     <string name="permission_photo_introduction">For saving images to Gallery and publishing statuses</string>
     <string name="permission_photo_video">Take photos and record video:</string>
     <string name="permission_photo_video_introduction">For taking photos, recording videos, and using flash</string>
     <string name="permission_picture_introduction">For saving, editing, and syncing photos and videos</string>
     <string name="permission_read_call_records">Edit call history:</string>
     <string name="permission_read_call_records_introduction">For adding items to call history and deleting blocked calls</string>
     <string name="permission_read_note_introduction">For accessing notes and attachments</string>
     <string name="permission_read_write_file">Access and save files and photos on your device:</string>
     <string name="permission_read_write_file_introduction">For accessing, saving, and caching items on your device</string>
     <string name="permission_recorder_file_introduction">For accessing and saving audio recordings</string>
     <string name="permission_recording">Record calls and audio:</string>
     <string name="permission_recording_introduction">For recording audio while recording video</string>
     <string name="permission_screen_shoot_introduction">For accessing and saving screen recordings</string>
     <string name="permission_send_message">Send SMS</string>
     <string name="permission_user_record_introduction">For recording audio</string>
     <string name="permission_virusscan_introduction">For performing virus scan and optimizing your device</string>
     <string name="permission_xunlei_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts in order to provide Xunlei services</string>
     <string name="protect_persoanl_info_statement">We shall protect your personal information in accordance with the relevant laws, regulations, and privacy policies.</string>
     <string name="recorder_introduction">You can use this app to record audio and back up recordings to the cloud.</string>
     <string name="require_authority_statement">To allow us to provide you with basic services, you need to grant the following permissions in order for us to collect your personal information:</string>
     <string name="require_network_authority_statement">To allow us to provide you with basic services, you need to connect to the internet and grant the following permissions in order for us to collect your personal information:</string>
     <string name="screen_recording_introduction">"This app allows you to record what's happening on your screen."</string>
     <string name="security_mobile_account_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts</string>
     <string name="service_agreement">"I've read and agreed to the terms and conditions."</string>
     <string name="service_name_album">Gallery</string>
     <string name="service_name_application_package">Package installer</string>
     <string name="service_name_calculator">Calculator</string>
     <string name="service_name_camera">Camera</string>
     <string name="service_name_carrier">Statement on carrier services</string>
     <string name="service_name_clock">Clock</string>
     <string name="service_name_compass">Compass</string>
     <string name="service_name_content_center">Content Center</string>
     <string name="service_name_download">Downloads</string>
     <string name="service_name_fast_application">Quick apps Framework</string>
     <string name="service_name_game">Games plug-in</string>
     <string name="service_name_google_service">Statement on Google services</string>
     <string name="service_name_location">Location-based services</string>
     <string name="service_name_lockscreen">Wallpaper Carousel</string>
     <string name="service_name_note">Notes</string>
     <string name="service_name_recorder">Recorder</string>
     <string name="service_name_screen_recording">Screen Recorder</string>
     <string name="service_name_security">Security</string>
     <string name="service_name_service_framework">Mi Services Framework</string>
     <string name="service_policy">&lt;Data&gt;Read and agree to our &amp;lt;a href=%1$s&amp;gt;Privacy Policy&amp;lt;/a &amp;gt;.&lt;/Data&gt;</string>
     <string name="service_privacy_index">Privacy Policy</string>
     <string name="servicestate_title">Statement on basic services</string>
     <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_message">Make sure you know how to use full screen gestures before selecting this option.</string>
     <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_negative_btn">Cancel</string>
     <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_positive_btn">OK</string>
     <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_title">Full screen gestures</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label_Mistore">, Mi Store system plug-in</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label_mab">, MAB</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label_package">, Package installer</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label_phrase">, Frequent phrases</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label_updater">, Updater</string>
</resources>
